MAXIME GALARNEAU

Level Designer

Portfolio: maximegalarneau.com Email: maxime.galarneau.ld@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/maxime-galarneau Phone: (438) 522-8335

About Me

My vast experience working with a variety of people has made me an excellent communicator as well as an organised hard worker who thrives with a committed team. I learned multiple skills in order to increase my value as a Level Designer. I am looking forward to further improved myself in the future.

Professional Experiences

<u>Lead Game Designer / Level Designer / Programmer</u> From April 2020 to Present

Campus ADN, Montreal

- Created and developed a full student's game in 15 weeks in a work-at-home environment
- Validated many aspects of the game to ensure they respect the game design
- Helped colleagues to resolve technical and level design troubles

Sales & Engineering Representative

From 2014 to 2019

Stelpro, Saint-Bruno-de-Montarville

- Represented products and the company's interests to customers and professionals alikes
- Assisted contractors and engineers to find solutions to their heating problems
- Followed many projects simultaneously to their completion at the customer's satisfaction
- Surpassed high monthly and annual sales objectives (Stelpro's Best Salesman of 2019)

Sales Representative

From 2011 to

2014

Vidéotron, Beloeil

- Represented company's products and plans according to customer's needs
- Solved customer's interrogations with great customer service
- Surpassed monthly & annual sales objectives (Vidéotron's Objective Exceedance Award of 2012 for my store)

Department Manager

From 2007 to 2011

Archambault, Boucherville

- Managed the personal with tasks, objectives and deadlines to respect

Tools Personal Skills

- Unreal Engine
- Unity
- Visual Studio
- Photoshop
- SketchUp
- 3DS max
- C# / C++

- Teamwork
- Strong Work Ethic
- Communication
- Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Time Management

Education

Level Design (AEC) - 2020

Campus ADN, Montreal

Political Science (Major) - 2014

UQAM, Montreal

Communication (Minor) - 2012

UQAM, Montreal

Arts, Letters & Communication - Profile Cinema (DEC) - 2009

Cégep St-Hyacinthe, St-Hyacinthe

Interests & Hobbies

- Video Games
- Comics
- Fishing
- Astronomy
- Politics, particularly international
- Skiing